(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-21T17:59:02.184644",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
あの交差点で みんながもしスキップをして
If everyone went skipping across that crosswalk,
もしあの街の真ん中で 手をつないで空を見上げたら
If we looked up at the skies in the center of the streets holding hands together.
もしあの街のどこかで チャンスがつかみたいのなら
If you want to take a chance somewhere on the streets
まだ泣くのには早いよね ただ前に進むしかないわ いやいや
Then it's too early to start crying. All you got to do is just to keep moving forward, oh well!
ポンポン 出してしまえばいいの
It's okay to keep popping out!
全然しないの つまんないでしょ
If you do nothing, it gets boring, doesn't it?
ヘッドフォンかけて リズムに乗せて
I put on my headphones and let myself get lost in the rhythm!
ウェイウェイ 空けて あたしの道を
Way, way, then I create my own road to follow
ポンポン 進む 色々なこと
All the things start to march on
どんどんキテる? あなたのキモチ
Have your feelings arrived so fast?
ポイポイ 捨てる 悪い子はだれ?
Poi-poi, who is the bad kid who likes to throw them away?
そうそう いいこ ああ
Yep, you're a good kid, ah
You Make Me Happy
Every Day PON
Every Time is PON
メリーゴーランド乗ってみたいの
I want to ride a merry-go-round!
Every Day PON
Every Time is PON
たぶんそんなんじゃ ダメでしょ
That's probably a bad idea, isn't it?
ポンポン 出してしまえばいいの
It's okay to keep popping out!
全然しないの つまんないでしょ
If you do nothing, it gets boring, doesn't it?
ヘッドフォンかけて リズムに乗せて
I put on my headphones and let myself get lost in the rhythm!
ウェイウェイ 空けて あたしの道を
Way, way, then I create my own road to follow
ポンポン うぇい うぇい うぇい
Pon-pon-way-way-way!
ポンポン うぇい PON うぇい ポンポン
Pon-pon-way-pon-way-pon-pon!
うぇい うぇい PON PON PON
Way-way-pon-pon-pon!
うぇい うぇい PON うぇい PON うぇい うぇい
Way-way-pon-way-pon-way-way!
あの交差点で みんながもしスキップをして
If everyone went skipping at that crosswalk
もしあの街の真ん中で 手をつないで空を見上げたら
If we looked up at the skies in the center of the streets holding hands together
もしあの街のどこかで チャンスがつかみたいのなら
If you want to take a chance somewhere on the streets
まだ泣くのには早いよね ただ前に進むしかないわ いやいや
Then it's too early to start crying. All you got to do is just to keep moving forward, oh well!
ポンポン 進む 色々なこと
All the things start to march on
どんどんキテる? あなたのキモチ
Have your feelings arrived so fast?
ポイポイ 捨てる 悪い子はだれ?
Poi-poi, who is the bad kid who likes to throw them away?
そうそう いいこ ああ
Yep, you're a good kid, ah
You Make Me Happy
Every Day PON
Every Time is PON
メリーゴーランド乗ってみたいの
I wanna ride a merry-go-round!
Every Day PON
Every Time is PON
たぶんそんなんじゃ ダメでしょ
That's probably a bad idea, isn't it?
ポンポン うぇい うぇい うぇい
Pon-pon-way-way-way!
ポンポン うぇい PON うぇい ポンポン
Pon-pon-way-pon-way-pon-pon!
うぇい うぇい PON PON PON
Way-way-pon-pon-pon!
うぇい うぇい PON うぇい PON うぇい うぇい
Way-way-pon-way-pon-way-way!
ポンポン うぇい うぇい うぇい
Pon-pon-way-way-way!
ポンポン うぇい PON うぇい ポンポン
Pon-pon-way-pon-way-pon-pon!
うぇい うぇい PON PON PON
Way-way-pon-pon-pon!
うぇい うぇい PON うぇい PON うぇい うぇい
Way-way-pon-way-pon-way-way!
That's right, I'm not just a detective!
I'm a time traveler! Watch this!
When we first met (hey hey!)
I wonder what you think of me
The image was set (hey hey!)
It was a perfect narrative
But as time went by, I forgot to hide
the laughs that came so naturally
Through lows and highs, I'd wonder why
I ever thought you would leave
Now no matter where or when we are, I know it's you I can count on
Now no matter where or when we are,
I know it's you I can count on.
Magical, mythical, nothing can stop us now, let's go!
Magical, mythical, nothing can stop us now,
Let's go!
Chikutaku, where'd the time go?
Wakuwaku, how should I know?
Why it seems when you're here with me the clock won't stop spinning?
Why it seems when you're here with me
The clock won't stop spinning?
Wapu wapu wapu wapu
Dokidoki, hearts beat faster
Tomodachi, friends forever
It's clear to see that this mystery was solved immediately
It's clear to see that this mystery
Was solved immediately,
Jikuu no yugami
It's been so long (hey hey!)
Since I laughed so hard I cried
Now you came along (hey hey!)
It happens almost every time
That I hear your voice, I'm left no choice but to let you know what you mean to me
That I hear your voice, I'm left no choice
To let you know what you mean to me.
Spiraling, time skipping
Through treasured memories
Now no matter where or when we're from, our friendship's elementary
Now no matter where or when we're from,
Our friendship's elementary.
Case closed, now you know, nothing can stop us now, let's go!
Case closed, now you know, nothing can stop us now,
Let's go!
Chikutaku, where'd the time go?
Wakuwaku, how should I know?
Why it seems when you're here with me the clock won't stop spinning?
Why it seems when you're here with me
The clock won't stop spinning?
Wapu wapu wapu wapu
Hey everyone!
It's me, Small Ame!
Small Ame's birthday, right?
Right?
Small Ame! Small Ame!
So, what do you guys think?
You like my new idol outfit?
Well, I guess it's time for this.
I gotta dance before I'm too!
Look at everyone so cute.
Okay Bubba, I think I'm ready. Hit the track, Bubba!
Okay Bubba, I think I'm ready.
Hit the track, Bubba!
Catch You Catch Me - Megumin Hinata
会いたいな 会えないな 切ないな この気持ち
I want to see you, but I can't... How sad, these feelings...
言えないの 言いたいな チャンス逃してばかり
I can't say it, but I want to.
I just keep letting my chance slip by.
だって だって 翼広げ二人で 空をマラソン 夢をユニゾンしたい
Together, let's spread our wings and marathon across the sky;
I want our dreams to be in unison.
ほら Catch You Catch You Catch Me Catch Me 待って
Hey look! Catch you, catch you, catch me, catch me, wait up!
こっちを向いて スキだといって
Look this way and say you like me.
そう Nice to Meet You Good to See You きっと
Yeah! Nice to meet you, good to see you, surely!
私の想い あなたのハートに飛んで飛んで飛んでいけ 迷わない
My thoughts will fly, fly, fly into your heart!
They will not get lost!
たまにね なくなっちゃう 身体のバッテリー
Sometimes, my batteries just run dry.
あなたの笑顔で いつも充電満タン パワー爆発しちゃえ
But with your smile, they're always fully charged, ready to explode!
お願い お願い まずは友達から
Please, please, we're friends first,
笑って 見つめて 楽しい毎日日にしたい
So I want to smile, look at you, and have fun every day.
ほら Catch You Catch You Catch Me Catch Me ゼッタイ
Hey look! Catch you, catch you, catch me, catch me, absolutely!
運命だって お似合いだって
It's our destiny. It suits us well.
そう Nice to Meet You Good to See You きっと
Yeah! Nice to meet you, good to see you, surely!
誰にも負けない あなたに世界で一番一番一番一番 恋してる
I won't give in to anyone. I'll be No.1 in the world to you!
I'm in love with you!
ほら Catch You Catch You Catch Me Catch Me 待って
Hey look! Catch you, catch you, catch me, catch me, wait up!
こっちを向いて スキだといって
Look this way and say you like me.
そう Nice to Meet You Good to See You きっと
Yeah! Nice to meet you, good to see you, surely!
私の想い あなたのハートに飛んで飛んで飛んでいけ 迷わない
My thoughts will fly, fly, fly into your heart!
They will not get lost!
ほら Catch You Catch You Catch Me Catch Me ゼッタイ
Hey look! Catch you, catch you, catch me, catch me, absolutely!
運命だって お似合いだって
It's our destiny. It suits us well.
So Nice to Meet You Good to See You きっと
So nice to meet you, good to see you, surely!
誰にも負けない あなたに世界で一番一番一番一番 恋してる
I won't give in to anyone. I'll be No.1 in the world to you!
I'm in love with you!
ほら Catch You Catch You Catch Me Catch Me ゼッタイ
Hey look! Catch you, catch you, catch me, catch me, absolutely!
運命だって お似合いだって
It's our destiny. It suits us well.
そう Nice to Meet You Good to See You きっと
So nice to meet you, good to see you, surely!
誰にも負けない あなたに世界で一番一番一番一番 恋してる
I won't give in to anyone. I'll be No.1 in the world to you!
I'm in love with you!
That's right, I'm not just a detective!
I'm a time traveler!
Watch this!
When we first met
I wonder what you'd think of me
The image was set
It was a perfect narrative
But as time went by
I forgot to hide
The laughs that came so naturally
Through lows and highs
I'd wonder why
I ever thought you would leave
Now no matter where or when we are
I know it's you I can count on
Magical
Mythical
Nothing can stop us now!
Let's go!
chikutaku
where 'd the time go ?
Where'd the time go?
waku waku
how should i know
why it seems
when you 're here with me
When you're here with me
the clock won't stop spinning ?
The clock won't stop spinning?
wapu wapu wapu wapu
doki doki
hearts beat faster
tomodachi
friends forever
it 's clear to see
It's clear to see
that this mystery
was solved immediately
jiku no yugami
ヤワなハートがしびれる
My weak little heart tingles,
心地よい針の刺激
the comfy prick of a needle
理由もないのに輝く
I light up for no reason at all.
それだけが愛のしるし
That alone is a sign of love
いつかあなたには
Someday, I'll come to you
すべて打ち明けよう
And tell you everything
少し強くなるために
To make myself a bit tougher
壊れたボートで一人漕いで行く
I paddle out alone on a broken board
夢の中でもわかる
I know it even in my dreams,
めくるめく夜の不思議
just how wondrous a radiant night can be
ただの思い出と
It's just a memory
風が囁いても
The wind may whisper
嬉し泣きの宝物
But my tears of joy are a treasure
何でもありそうな国で
In a land with nearly everything,
ただ一つ
you'll only find one
ヤワなハートがしびれる
My weak little heart tingles,
心地よい針の刺激
the comfy prick of a needle
理由もないのに輝く
I light up for no reason at all.
それだけが愛のしるし
That alone is a sign of love
それだけで愛のしるし
That alone shows it is a sign of love
同じ未来を見たい
I want to see the same future,
あの夢手に入れよう
Let's get our hands on that dream.
それぞれ違ったココロで走れ go
Running with different hearts, go!
どこを見ても真っ暗な
No matter where you look,
場所に芽生えていた
hope was sprouting in that dark place.
ほんの小さな希望にこの瞳奪われた
This gaze was stolen
不安で揺るがる心をうまくチューニングして
Tuning my anxious, trembling heart,
ほんの小さな勇気を振り絞っていたよ
I was gathering a little courage.
諦めの文字 デリートして進む
Deleting the words of giving up, I press on.
苦しいときも もう私は ひとりじゃないから
Even when times are hard, I'm not alone anymore,
だからもっと夢追いかけたい ワクワク止まらない
So I want to chase my dreams even more, waku waku won't stop!
想像超えてく 世界 見せてあげる
I'll show you a world beyond imagination.
アクセスしてみたい？ 後悔なんてそうさせない
I want to access it, there's no room for regret.
それぞれ違ったココロで走れ go
Running with different hearts, go!
仮想の空に輝く 眩しい想いは
Dazzling thoughts shining in the virtual sky,
見たことのない 光をリアルに届けるよ
bringing unseen light into reality.
いつも聞こえるエールは ここにキャプチャーして
Capturing every cheer we always hear right here,
また新しい光を 探したくなるよ
I want to search for a new light.
that’s right , i’m not just a detective !
That's right, I'm not just a detective!
i’m a time traveler ! watch this !
I'm a time traveler! Watch this!
when we first met ( hey hey ! )
When we first met (Hey, hey!)
i wonder what you think of me
the image was set ( hey hey ! )
The image was set (Hey, hey!)
it was a perfect narrative
but as time went by , i forgot to hide
But as time went by, I forgot to hide
the laughs that came so naturally
through lows and highs , i’d wonder why
Through lows and highs, I'd wonder why
i ever thought you would leave
now no matter where or when we are
i know it’s you i can count on
I know it's you I can count on
magical , mythical
Magical, mythical
nothing can stop us now
let’s go !
Let's go!
chikutaku , where’d the time go ?
Chikutaku, where'd the time go?
wakuwaku , how should i know ?
Wakuwaku, how should I know?
why it seems when you’re here with me
Why it seems when you're here with me
the clock won’t stop spinning ?
The clock won't stop spinning?
wapu wapu wapu wapu
dokidoki , hearts beat faster
Dokidoki, hearts beat faster
tomodachi , friends forever
Tomodachi, friends forever
it’s clear to see that this mystery
It's clear to see that this mystery
was solved immediately
jikuu no yugami
it’s been so long ( hey hey ! )
It's been so long (Hey, hey!)
since i laughed so hard i cried
now you came along ( hey hey ! )
Now you came along (Hey, hey!)
it happens almost every time
that i hear your voice , i’m left no choice
That I hear your voice, I'm left no choice
but to let you know what you mean to me
spiraling , time skipping
Spiraling, time skipping
through treasured memories
now no matter where or when we’re from
Now no matter where or when we're from
our friendship’s elementary
Our friendship's elementary
case closed , now you know
Case closed, now you know
nothing can stop us now
let’s go !
Let's go!
chikutaku , where’d the time go ?
Chikutaku, where'd the time go?
wakuwaku , how should i know ?
Wakuwaku, how should I know?
why it seems when you’re here with me
Why it seems when you're here with me
the clock won’t stop spinning ?
The clock won't stop spinning?
wapu wapu wapu wapu
dokidoki , hearts beat faster
Dokidoki, hearts beat faster
tomodachi , friends forever
Tomodachi, friends forever
it’s clear to see that this mystery
It's clear to see that this mystery
was solved immediately
jikuu no yugami
though each day we’re older
Though each day we're older
what the future holds is not not not for us to know yet
What the future holds is not for us to know yet
it’s gone gone gone before we know it
It's gone before we know it
so let’s solve the question
So let's solve the question
we can make each second
chikutaku , last forever
Chikutaku, last forever
wakuwaku , it’s now or never !
Wakuwaku, it's now or never!
chikutaku , where’d the time go ?
Chikutaku, where'd the time go?
wakuwaku , how should i know ?
Wakuwaku, how should I know?
why it seems when you’re here with me
Why it seems when you're here with me
the clock won’t stop spinning ?
The clock won't stop spinning?
wapu wapu wapu wapu
dokidoki , hearts beat faster
Dokidoki, hearts beat faster
tomodachi , friends forever
Tomodachi, friends forever
it’s clear to see that this mystery
It's clear to see that this mystery
was solved immediately
jikuu no yugami
that’s right , i’m not just a detective !
That's right, I'm not just a detective!
i’m a time traveler ! look at this !
I'm a time traveler! Look at this!
“Ookami Blues”
Rina Kino
[Title: Ookami Blues]
ううるううる寂しい ウルフ です
Tearing up, I am a lonely wolf,
無理にでも群りたくて飛びついて
I want to forcefully herd, I jump on you.
巻きたり振ったり垂れちゃうしっぽ
My tail rolls up, wags, and dangles.
オオカミ ブルース
Wolf Blues
遠くに仲間に届くかな
Will my howl reach my comrades?
ひとしきり遠吠えたぎり観光鳥
I howled for a while, but no response.
いいもん 一匹の王国ダンジョン
That's fine, a one-wolf dungeon kingdom,
オオカミ プリンセス
Wolf Princess
ごはんがポロリ 涙もポロリ
I drop my food, I drop my tears, too.
今日の骨の味はしょっぱいな
My bone tastes so salty today.
明日目覚めたらフェロモンが
My plan is when I wake up tomorrow
あふれてメロメロにする予定
My pheromones will overflow.
後で泣かされても知らないもんね
I don't care if you cry later.
また明日
See you tomorrow.
カミカミ言われるオオカミは
A wolf who's been called as a god,
寝にもたづさばさばで仲直り
Doesn't hold grudges, makes up easily.
喧嘩のわけも忘れてたろっ て
Did you forget why we were fighting?
エスパーですか
Are you a psychic?
主役はズバリ ウルフで決まり
The wolf is chosen as the main character.
モフモフして今日も起立礼ご
Fluff fluff, stand, bow and go again.
暴れ牙 楽しい
Get wild, exert, it's fun.
ハガレビビリ 一緒に
Get separated and scared together.
みんな本当は優しい
They all are actually kind.
だからほら私がボスになってあげる
So I will be your boss.
このしっぽに続け
Follow my tail.
ううるううる寂しい ウルフ です
Tearing up, I am a lonely wolf.
振り向けば ひとりきり 観光鳥
When I turn around, I'm all alone.
巻きたり振ったり垂れちゃうしっぽ
My tail rolls up, wags, and dangles.
オオカミ ブルース
Wolf Blues
また来週
See you next week.
ナゾナゾみたいに地球儀を解き明かしたら
If we solve the globe like a riddle,
みんなでどこまででも行けるね
we can go anywhere together.
ワクワクしたいと願いながら過してたよ
I spent my time wishing to be excited.
かなえてくれたのは誰なのかな?
Who granted my wish?
時間の果てまでBoooon!!
To the end of time, boooom!
ワープでループなこの想いは
This feeling of warping and looping
何もかもを巻き込んだ想像で遊ぼう
lets us play with wild imagination!
ある晴れた日のこと
On a certain sunny day,
魔法以上の快楽が
more delightful than magic,
限りなく降りそそぐ 不可能じゃないわ
endlessly pouring down—it's not impossible!
明日また会うとき 笑いながらhumming
When we meet again tomorrow, smiling and humming,
うれしさを集めよう
let's gather up our happiness!
カンタンなんだよこんなの
It's so easy like this—
追いかけてねつかまえてみて
chase after it and try to catch it!
大きな夢&夢好きでしょう?
You love big dreams, don't you?
いろいろ予想ができそうでできない未来
A future that seems predictable yet unpredictable,
それでもひとつだけわかるよ
but there's still one thing I know:
キラキラ光って熱い雲の上を飾る星たちが希望をくれる
Sparkling stars decorate the hot clouds, giving us hope.
時間に乗ろうよびゅーーーん!!
Let's ride on time, whoosh!
チープでクールな年頃も 寂しがっちゃ恥ずかしいよなんてね言わせて
At this cool and edgy age, feeling lonely is embarrassing... or so they say.
手と手をつないだら 向かうトコ敵でしょ?
When we hold hands, we're unstoppable!
輝いた瞳には不可能なかないの
In those shining eyes, nothing is impossible.
上だけ見ていると涙も乾いちゃう 変わりたい
If you only look up, even tears dry up. I want to change.
心から強く思うほど伝わる 走り出すよ後ろの人もおいでよ
The stronger I feel it, the more it shows. Start running—come on, those in the back too!
ドキドキするでしょ Boooon!!
It's exciting, right? Boooom!
ワープでループなこの想いは
This feeling of warping and looping
何もかもを巻き込んだ想像で遊ぼう
lets us play with wild imagination!
ある晴れた日のこと
On a certain sunny day,
魔法以上の快楽が
more delightful than magic,
限りなく降りそそぐ 不可能じゃないわ
endlessly pouring down—it's not impossible!
明日また会うとき 笑いながらhumming
When we meet again tomorrow, smiling and humming,
うれしさを集めよう
let's gather up our happiness!
カンタンなんだよこんなの
It's so easy like this—
追いかけてねつかまえてみて
chase after it and try to catch it!
大きな夢&夢好きでしょう?
You love big dreams, don't you?
いろいろ予想ができそうでできない未来
A future that seems predictable yet unpredictable,
それでもひとつだけわかるよ
but there's still one thing I know:
キラキラ光って熱い雲の上を飾る星たちが希望をくれる
Sparkling stars decorate the hot clouds, giving us hope.
時間に乗ろうよびゅーーーん!!
Let's ride on time, whoosh!
チープでクールな年頃も 寂しがっちゃ恥ずかしいよなんてね言わせて
At this cool and edgy age, feeling lonely is embarrassing... or so they say.
手と手をつないだら 向かうトコ敵でしょ?
When we hold hands, we're unstoppable!
輝いた瞳には不可能なかないの
In those shining eyes, nothing is impossible.
上だけ見ていると涙も乾いちゃう 変わりたい
If you only look up, even tears dry up. I want to change.
心から強く思うほど伝わる 走り出すよ後ろの人もおいでよ
The stronger I feel it, the more it shows. Start running—come on, those in the back too!
ドキドキするでしょ Boooon!!
It's exciting, right? Boooom!
捕まえてみて大きな夢夢好きでしょう?
Try to catch it—you love big dreams, don't you?
大きな夢夢好きでしょう?
You love big dreams, don't you?
Oh, thank you everyone for coming!
All right, you guys can go now. Later!
All right, you guys know what time it's for? Merch! That's right!
Birthday merch, what could it be? Tada!
Amelia Watson starter pack!
And what's the special item you say?
Bubba shoulder special item, and... tada!
Your very own Amelia Watson dakimakura!
Drawn by Nabi-mama, thank you so much Nabi-mama, it's so cute!
And uh, we have something else, right? You must be thinking, "Ame, well this doesn't really improve my daily life that much."
What else can I use? Tada! We have the Watson's Task Manager along with some beautiful, cute magnets!
And... the number one item I can't wait to show you guys, the Squishy Bubba Night Lamp!
Oh my god, it's so squishy and round, I just wanna... Thank you guys for coming to 3D Birthday Live, I really appreciate all of your support!
And, to be honest,
I'm actually in Japan right now 'cause I snuck into big Ame's luggage,
and, yeah, we're gonna go on over
to Ame in Japan! Live to the Ame in Japan!
All right, bye everyone!
Thank you guys so much! Thank you, Kanata-ru, and thank you...
Thank you everybody for watching! I love you guys!
Thank you, thank you! Bye-bye! Yay!
Hello? Hello? Hello?
Oh my god, I'm here!
Hi everyone!
Can you guys hear me?
Test, test, hello!
Ahem! Ahem! Ahem!
Thank you, Small Ame, for that wonderful introduction.
Thank you guys for all the birthday wishes! Thank you, thank you, thank you!
There's so much to talk about after that, oh my god.
Whoa, so as Small Ame said, I'm actually in Japan right now!
Yatta! They let me in!
The best birthday gift ever!
Uh, what'd you guys think?
Was it a pretty good concert, right?
A nice little bite-sized mini-live.
Happy birthday, oh thank you, thank you, thank you!
As you can see, we also have a new background by Melon Turtle and huge shout out to Kanata-ru
uh for, you know, taking care of all of the mocap data for that concert.
Uh, thank you guys.
I'm glad you had fun.
I'm glad you had so much fun.
I'm glad you guys enjoyed.
Do I sound okay?
Does the mic sound okay?
Test, test.
You love the live?
Oh, thank you, thank you!
Oh, my hat's cut off a little bit.
Let me fix that.
Yeah? Sounds good?
Okay, sweet.
Oh, I was gonna add something else, so, yes, I'm in Japan right now.
I wanted to go over the merch again because
Small Ame did it like super, super fast.
Um, so let's go over the merch again.
Uh, really quick, let's see, uh, the slideshow.
Oops.
Don't mind, don't mind, don't mind.
All right, let me restart it.
Will this restart it?
All right, let me bring up the image manually so we can take a look.
Uh, thank you guys.
The static, yeah, was it getting crunchy at all during the...
It's, uh, it's getting a little crunchy sometimes.
I don't know why it does that.
Um, but it goes away after a little bit.
All right, so the first item in the merch...
Um, yeah, a dakimakura.
Dakimakura drawn by Nabi-mama.
Let's zoom in on this.
Ooh, ooh, oh, damn!
So this is, uh, actually a cover, you'd have to get the pillow separately, but you can get the cover if any of you guys are interested in that.
And then after that, I think these items should be up for sale in one minute if you want.
If you want, you don't have to, of course.
But then also, there's this, uh...
This is actually a magnet.
And this is like something to put on your fridge and, uh, write down the tasks that you got to do for the day, right?
The Ame toes, yeah, they're covered, unfortunately for you
sick ones out there.
Um, yeah, this one's, uh, a task manager, it's a magnet, and it comes with a small Ame pen, look at her.
Um, so yeah, this is, uh, pretty useful, you know, help you finish your tasks.
And here's also these, uh, magnets, which look at them, so cute.
These are magnets to go along with the set.
So cute! And then, my favorite item personally is this Bubba lamp.
Look at the Bubba lamp!
It, it lights up, and it's also a little squishy.
Squishy Bubba lamp.
Um, please do not dent his face, okay?
Yeah, this one's really cool. All the items are available for purchase separately.
Um, so you can get this just by itself if you don't want the dakimakura or any of the other stuff.
That's totally fine, I'm pretty sure they're available for purchase separately.
Yeah, I gotta take good care of the lamp.
That's right.
Head pats only, don't punch it, okay?
All right, the merch is live.
All the links are in the description, it'll be up live for one month if you guys need to save a little bit.
Uh, you can save.
And then finally, if you decide you want to get everything all together...
get a little tiny dakimakura card,
which has my signature back there and a special message,
which is uh I don't want to spoil it for you guys, so
you gotta wait until you get it and uh one year—
no, hopefully it won't take that long. Yeah, sorry about the static.
I don't know why it does that. It does it every now and again.
I hope it's not that bad. I don't think it's part of the BGM.
I think it's just the audio setup that I'm using, so sorry, sorry, sorry.
Um, so yeah, that's pretty much everything.
I'm going to put the slideshow back up here.
Birthday celebration!
And yeah, oh, what did you guys think of the uh— what do you guys think?
Here, I'm going to bring it— I'm going to bring it up here.
Here, let's switch to here, actually.
Alright, let's do this.
I think I forgot to put chat in myself on the screen. Oops!
Very busy day.
Um, but I hope you guys enjoyed the birthday concert. It was a lot of uh recording and stuff.
So yeah, we'll talk about that now.
Uh at the start, did you guys get to play this game?
Did you guys get to play with the uh claw machine?
This was really cool uh to work on.
It's actually interactive, so if you guys put in controls in the chat,
like forward, grab, left, right, um up, down, I think.
I don't know about up-down.
But yeah, this is uh something that I wanted to show.
I wanted to show grab, grab.
What are you guys going to grab?
There's actually some— there might be some surprise—
What do you guys— oh, is it time for that, huh?
Got Watson concoction!
I'm just kidding. I don't have anything planned for that. It's just— I think there's some random items in there.
So yeah, you guys can control this. Um this is going to be our new intro screen.
And it'll be really fun like if there's a day where you guys get to decide what I wear for my hat,
you know, like what I wear um I think that'll be really cool.
I do have some more— I have another announcement, but I'm going to do it in a little bit after some chatting.
And I guess there's some fan-made projects that you guys worked together on that we're going to take a look at. I believe there's a VR chat world and there's also a fan book.
So we'll probably do that um see I'm going to put down the recap here.
Because I think that—
Okay, it's it's gone, it's gone.
I think the the recap will help because people will tune in and they'll be like, what where's the 3D live? Well, you missed it.
So we're going to put the recap here. We're going to type there so that they know that they missed it.
And then what's up next on the list?
Why don't we put up this down here?
What did you guys get now?
Alright, we'll put it right here, yeah, that way you guys can still play while I'm doing this recap thing, okay?
Alright, recap, 3D live.
Maybe I should get a little checkmark symbol in here.
I do have another announcement um besides all this. I know we've already had so many new things, right?
So many new things. 3D live, check.
Recap, check.
Merch, merch announcement, check.
Announced that I'm in Japan. Japan, check.
Yeah, I wanted to I wanted to tell you guys a little bit about how Japan is. So we'll talk about that.
Uh let me put this back here.
Merch announcement, Japan check.
Uh what else should I put on this recap? I guess we haven't really done so much.
Yet? Did you guys get my hat? You found my hat? That must be my spare then.
Uh okay, so yeah, I'm in Japan now, and I actually already met up with uh Mumei and Kiara.
And yeah, it was fun, and Mumei and I went to eat at one of those conveyor belt places with sushi. That was fun.
Uh I haven't met anyone else yet, but I'm still— I have only been here for like a few days.
So uh I just been exploring and it's been really cool.
It's crazy. Japan is pretty crazy.
It's really cool.
It feels like unreal that I'm here, you know? It's like a dream. It's like a dream.
you know, gotten here is with you guys.
You know, getting here is with you guys,
and you're all your support and making it possible. So thank you.
and all your support in making it possible. So thank you.
I never, I don't know, even though like at the start...
ちょっと待って。ちょっと待ってください。
Wait a minute. Please wait a minute.
あの、いまは
Uh, right now...
いま、アメは
Right now, Ame is
日本です。
in Japan.
そして国を...
And the country...
めっちゃ... めっちゃかっこいい！
is super... super cool!
あ、日本の食べ物が美味しい。
Ah, Japanese food is delicious.
めっちゃ美味しい。
Super delicious.
How do I say...
Let me translate.
あ、日本の建築は
Ah, Japanese architecture
かっこいい！
is so cool!
シティプランニング、すごい！
City planning is amazing!
How do I say...
列車はすごい！
Trains are amazing!
Yeah, everything is really cool here.
日本のコンビニの食べ物は
Japanese convenience store food
めっちゃ美味しい。めっちゃ美味しい。
is super delicious. Super delicious.
すごく美味しい！
Extremely delicious!
Yeah, it's really cool.
Yeah, when I first got here, it was really nice.
I mean it's still really nice, but there's so much food everywhere.
All the food everywhere you go, it's like it smells good, it tastes good.
And actually, I have an announcement. I have an announcement, a very cool announcement.
And actually, I have an announcement. A very cool announcement.
The bread here,
for some reason, okay, you guys are going to think I'm crazy or lying,
but it doesn't make me sick!
I haven't been sick! And I I I've been eating a ton of bread.
I haven't been sick! And I I've been eating a ton of bread.
ちょっと待ってください！
Please wait a minute!
あ！
Ah!
Yeah, I don't know what it is. Maybe I've been walking, I've been eating healthier.
Maybe that helps. Yeah, I'm not sure, but it's been really cool.
Let's see. My favorite thing that I had so far,
I had curry udon, that was really, really, really, really tasty.
Oh, it was so good.
I'm so happy I was able to eat it.
I don't know if it made me sick or not, but it was really fun.
So yeah, I'm I'm planning to meet some other uh Hololive members um soon.
But uh I think I do have a collab stream planned uh coming soon, so you guys will have to wait and see.
And now, I do have another announcement.
But first, I guess I'll take a look at some fan stuff. Hi.
食べ物、食べ物が美味しい。
Food, food is delicious.
All right, one second. Do you guys have any questions for me while we wait?
Oh, yeah, and this venny uh sorry, this claw machine was made by Nalref Repro. I think I said his name right.
Oh, yeah, and this ven- uh sorry, this claw machine was made by Nalref Repro. I think I said his name right.
And uh does, I don't know them, but does...
I will make a Twitter post after this and link them.
Did I go to the arcades? Oh, yeah.
Oh, my god, I spent so much
I spent so much money at the claw machines because they're so fun
and they have these little tiny claw machines that are probably meant for kids 'cause they have little stepping stools.
But I spent so much
I spent so much money at the vending machine claw machines 'cause they're so fun.
How was the flight? Well, I just slept a lot.
I just slept and played Switch 'cause as you guys know we have the Mario Kart tournament later,
which I will be participating in, but um I'm not gonna stream my perspective 'cause I didn't bring my capture card.
So, yeah, I'm just gonna be playing...
um, yeah.
I'll be in my hotel chillin' and playing Mario Kart.
We'll be gaming.
Any nice moss?
I've only seen one thing of moss,
and I touched it and it was pretty soft.
It was pretty soft.
No, this is not pre-recorded. It's not.
How could it be pre-recorded?
Look, you guys are like trying to control the claw machine right now.
See?
Isn't it addicting?
It's very addicting.
Did I keep any dirt?
No, apparently you're not supposed to bring any plants or dirt back.
I don't know, maybe dirt is okay.
Oh...
You dead! You dead! You dead! You dead!
But every time I try to buy something, it's like I encounter two types of people...
Oh, Bubba!
I encounter two types of people while I'm buying stuff here in Japan.
It's like I say, I ask them a question, oh, like I had to buy a hard drive, so I was like,
"Sumimasen, pasokon no hato doraibu wa doko desu ka?"
And so... they might try to respond like in Japanese,
but one thing I didn't account for is everybody speaks really fast, so I'm just like trying to listen.
I'm like, "Hai, hai. Oh, sumimasen!"
"Wakarimasen."
Oh, but then there's another type,
yeah, where they just immediately, as soon as I speak, they pull out their phone and they use Google Translate.
Uh, "Arigatou gozaimasu!"
Yeah, yeah.
But it's it makes me so nervous
'cause, you know, even when I speak English, I'll stutter when I'm speaking to new people and I'll mess up what I'm saying,
so, you know, in another language I'm like, ah, I always mess something up even though I practice in my head and I think it's fine.
I just need to practice more.
And Google Translate, "tasukaru." "Tasukaru!"
All right, I have the fanbook here.
Oh, I just got to practice more, right?
So far I've only seen um I guess like, you know, more urban places. Yeah?
I want to see more like trees and stuff, but maybe I'll go to a park or something.
Quick, everybody go to the park!
All right, apparently you guys made um a birthday book.
A birthday book!
It's a PDF.
I'm downloading it now.
Yeah, I saw um Kiara and Mumei... I don't know... I think Kiara talked about it a little bit.
But yeah, we went to the arcade.
We mostly just did claw machines there.
We didn't really play...
Oh, we played Mario Kart and Kiara won. Okay, she won this time.
But uh I was I kept using abilities on me
'cause I was in front, I was first a lot of the time.
And so, you know, if you're first,
you end up getting hit with the most items, and
she got it.
She got it right at the right at the end.
Ow! My ears!
All right, let me try to add this.
Okay, we're going to switch to the we're going to switch to the intro screen for just a second while we like add this fanbook thing.
Starting technically... Here we go. Now you guys can still play.
Okay, let me make the recap text smaller.
All right, I'm going to take a look at this fan stuff.
Thank you guys so much for um all of the all of the super chats and all the support. And...
And thank you for all the birthday wishes.
And thank you for all the memberships, and thank you, thank you, thank you.
Without you guys, I wouldn't have been able to get this far celebrating our third birthday together... Is it our third birthday together?
Our third one.
So, uh, hontou ni arigatou gozaimasu.
Yes, wow, our third birthday together. It went by pretty fast, huh?
It did go by pretty fast.
All right, so let's take a look at this fanbook. I don't know, some of you guys may have contributed.
I think there's a scroll function here, let's see.
Oh yeah.
Whoa, don't look, don't look, don't look, don't look.
I'm just kidding, I'll let you guys look just for today, okay?
Wow, look how pretty.
Illustration by Ardenlorol.
(laughs) Ow, it tick, it tick, it tick.
Foreword, Teamates Case File number two.
This book was made for the one and only Amelia Watson, including Connor for the 3D VRC map portion...
of the project. I don't know if we'll be able to look at the VRC map today, I'm not sure if I'll have any time.
But, um...
Yeah, I definitely want to take a look at it on stream at some point. So yeah, yeah, yeah, that'll be really fun.
Messages within this book from Teamates are for the eyes only, only for the eyes of Ame.
Wait, does that mean I can't stream it?
Oh wow, you guys are you guys are put on the spot now.
Put on the spot now!
Front cover art, rear cover art, page design, assets.
Thank you, thank you.
Only one copy of the book will be printed, which will be sent to you, Ame number 1 through 1337.
That's me!
Uh uh uh, just in case this one has been lost in another timeline, burned by Small Ame, stolen by B. Ame.
Yes, the digital copy!
You guys are all put on the spot now.
To all Ames who have their birthday on January 6th, this project was made in group pods especially for you by Teamates all over the globe.
This is our way to say thank you for all that you do for us. You mean a lot to every Teamate and this is our way to show it.
Everyone involved has worked incredibly hard to make this gift, which goes to show how special this community is...
Hold on, let me help you guys out, hold on.
For those of you guys still playing, you try to get every item. I think there's some pretty rare items in there so that you guys haven't gotten yet in the claw machine.
Excuse me.
Grab!
What is that?
Woah! My hat! You guys already got that one already? How many versions do you need a hat? Is that it?
Uh, okay, let's see. As mentioned before, this project also includes a 3D VRC map, so we hope you can check it out if you have some time.
This book contains the art from that map, but we still hope you check the map out.
We apologize for it being kind of scuffed you weren't able to find the book. We hope you enjoy your gifts nonetheless.
It's okay. Scuffed is par for the course, par for the course.
Hold on, let me drink some water though.
Par for the EN course, right? Oh, my magnifying glass!
Uh, your teammates always look forward to spending more time with you, and we can't wait to see more of your achievements in the future.
Aw, thank you. Oh, cute!
Shuuzo!
Whoa! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Thank you for always bringing joy to everyone with your stream. I can't express how much we appreciate your hard work on trying to push the boundaries of EN VTubing, setting up collabs with your coworkers.
To me personally, you were my first time someone used my art for thumbnail and gave me the greatest joy and motivation to continue grinding my art skill.
I'm happy to see how much you've grown well from debut.
Aw, that's so sweet.
Thank you!
And a message... sorry, I think my computer's lagging a little bit. Here we go. Thank you for always bringing joy to everyone...
Ame, awesome, beyond comprehension, truly one of kind human, even if you're British. (laughs)
Kidding aside, you have gone beyond measure in your endeavors as an idol, a detective, and a friend. I wish you the happiness of all time, timelines combined...
Please know no matter into what adventures you get into, your investigation will always be cheering and supporting you all the way!
Aw, thank you!
constant source of enjoyment
Ah you guys are too sweet, just- just sweet!
You guys got Bubba.
I miss Bubba. Bubba's doing good though.
Bubba is being watched over by Brother Watson, so Bubba's having a good time.
Yeah, Bubba really likes him, so he's doing good.
And he's doing models, off-collab, Collab with JPC, seniors, despite language barriers.
Yes. Now we'll hopefully at some point,
not hopefully, there will be um at least one off-collab that I have planned. So hope you guys look forward to that.
Watching improve your skills from debut, always willing to help, not only your genmates, but other Holomembers in general.
Oh, thank you, thank you.
You guys are gonna- you guys are gonna have make my head way too big. Look at it, it's already too big!
You guys are gonna- you guys are gonna make my head way too big. Look at it, it's already too big!
Ain't cute. Keep reaching for the stars, Ame.
Oh, thank you. Oh, I like this one on Twitter.
Ah yes, a comic artist, sincerely an Ame fan.
At least you can come up with those were super creative, but the scene action, all of them worked out the way you intended,
so you keep going. I think the uh...
I hope the concert, yeah.
It turned out pretty good, right?
I did a lot of mocap recording for it and it took me a long time to record the songs 'cause I I like record each song, will probably take me somewhere between like three to six hours,
because I record it and I'm just like, no, this is not it.
This is not it. And so I keep going,
and then I look at the time and I'm like, oh my god, I've been doing this for over two hours and then I keep going
until I get something I'm satisfied with.
And my mic doesn't get static, it's just the BGM. Okay, let's get to know.
Oh, thank you.
I love the Gator animation where you guys slap it to grab it. The bee Ame! The bee Ame!
Oh, you guys are so sweet. Thank you, thank you.
Feliz cumpleaños!
Muchas gracias. You know, actually,
when I was when I like buy something here in Japan,
I I'll be saying like, hi, hi, and...
and like it's happened twice already where I accidentally went like, C, C, uh hi, hi,
Pardon. Sumimasen.
Saturday of March last year when I fell hard down rabbit hole, I spent all day watching everything Hololive EN related and I got to see and all the things you did for your genmates.
It was an awe. You became my favorite. At the moment, my name is only Crystal with time.
You built a 3D studio, yeah.
Yes, I used uh the Ame studio for the concert.
I don't know if you guys can tell the hands are a little- I still need to work on the hand mocap,
but uh everything else I thought looked pretty good. There were like some hiccups
every now and again with like an arm or two, or...
But yeah, um I thought it turned out really nice, especially like on my official uh 3D model, I thought it turned out really nice.
Yeah, huge shout-out to Connor. That was actually my first time watching it with you guys and I was like laughing.
I love the small Ame idol outfit, uh that was by seafoam. I'd like to use that again at a later date 'cause it's really cute.
And we only got to see it for one song. Ah!
I'm glad you guys liked it.
I love your karaokes, I love all the different Ames you come up with, I love secret endings, I love when you speak Spanish, huh.
Sí, sí, muchas gracias para venir a mi cumpleaños.
How do you say party? Ame fiesta! Ame fiesta! Ame fiesta! Ame fiesta!
Oh, thank you. So sweet.
The Pie maker, thank you, thank you.
Oh, cute!
I like the hair like this, all curly.
Ame fiesta! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Hello, happy birthday Ame! Started to watch your streams more religiously back in March, became a member after seeing all the fun VR stuff you done.
Oh, thank you! Similar hobbies!
Thank you for your membership!
Oh, a gator, what was that?
A gator what? I haven't seen that one yet. Is that a new one?
Gator plushie.
Aww...
Aww, so sweet. Wishing you brightened up my day.
Thank you so much for being an amazing person. Aww, proud to be an investigator.
So cute, thank you.
Are you guys just spamming grab? No, you guys are planning this right?
A few of you playing.
Thank you, thank you.
Albert. And prosperous growth of the channel and community.
Aww, you guys got it again twice in a row.
Is that a sign? Should we have- we should maybe we should get a gator plushie.
And I still have one more announcement left. What could it be?
And just kidding. It's not more merch.
Uh, by the way, the merch is- I think I'm blocking it with my head, huh?
Hold on. I'll just go a little bit like this.
The merch is on sale, yeah. There's the links underneath the stream. Oh, you know, if anyone's interested in that, I'm just saying.
Um, but thank you. Hold on. Let me read. Um, is only can congratulate you and thank you because your streams light up my day.
Aww, you guys are so sweet. I'm glad you enjoy the streams. Thank you, thank you.
Hope you're all having a beautiful day too. Ah...
What happens? How can we put a timer on for how often the audio- it's like on a cycle or something?
I was hearing this all throughout the concert. I'm glad you guys couldn't hear that.
Aww, cute.
Look how time flies, Ame. It's already been three years. Thank you for your hardworking spirit, for everyone entertaining.
Please just drink more water, right?
I actually have. Hold on. Let me get something. My version of a cake, which I got from the combini,
is a fruit sando. Which I don't think it makes me sick. I don't know. I don't want to get too TMI with you guys,
but you know, as investigators, you know, obviously since I have my PDF, uh, and I'm also a doctor,
you guys are also a doctor, so maybe your opinion would be helpful.
Okay, right? I don't know if I want to share details, but okay.
You know when you eat something, okay, and later like between three to eight hours later, hopefully, you know, you go to the bathroom, right?
And something might come out or might not. If you're an idol, definitely nothing would come out. Okay?
You know the color can change depending on what you eat, right? Okay, well,
sometimes with people that are allergic to bread, they eat bread and they have to go to the bathroom right away and it makes them really sick. But for me, it's the opposite. It's actually the opposite.
Um, okay. I don't go to the bathroom, right? Cuz I'm an idol. Okay? You guys get what I'm getting at?
But when I eat the bread at home, it makes my tummy hurt, and it makes it like all, you know, the stuff that comes out, it's like a different weird color, okay?
But then when I eat the bread here, everything's normal. So I think it's all déjà vu is what I'm trying to say.
So I have a fruit sando here, which is my cake. I wanted to put some cakes from Twitter on the screen, but I kind of ran out of time.
Is it okay with you guys? Just play- just play the claw machine. It's like when a-
It's like when a mom, or like a parent, you know, they're- they're busy with something, so they're just- they give their kid an iPad. Okay, can you guys- you guys look at the iPad.
I'm gonna try this fruit sando while I search for a cake to put on the screen.
The fruit sandwiches here are so good.
Is the static like really loud? Are you getting like an ASMR feeling from it?
It's nice static. Are you getting like an ASMR feeling from it?
Not loud? Just a little bit weird. Can you rewind and see if it's on the track?
Loud, but bearable.
fried, right?
I still haven't eaten like, um
I want to have tempura udon.
But I haven't eaten any yet.
But when Mumei and I went to conveyor belt sushi,
they had like a tempura fried shrimp.
It was so good.
It was so tasty.
I want more. I want more.
I also had um, even though I... even though okay,
you know like uh they have ekiben, which is like the type of bento that you eat while you're on like the Shinkansen or something.
you know, like, they have ekiben, which is like the type of bento that you eat while you're on the Shinkansen or something.
I think, ekiben, ekibento? It's like a bento you're supposed to eat while you're on a train.
Well, I was just like exploring around and I saw like a place selling them
Well, I was just exploring around and I saw a place selling them
while I was like trying to get on a train.
while I was trying to get on a train.
And uh I ate one and it was so good.
And I ate one and it was so good.
Oh, it had like fried rice and it had like a little tiny fried um what is it called?
Oh, it had like fried rice and it had a little tiny fried... um, what is it called?
katsu...
but like a pork... I forgot what it's called.
katsu,
katsudon?
katsudon, karaage... did it have a piece of karaage too? Is it really tasty? Tonkatsu, tonkatsu.
katsudon, karaage... did it have a piece of karaage too? It was really tasty. Tonkatsu, tonkatsu.
Yeah, even though it was like cold, it wasn't like crunchy or fresh, it was still so tasty.
Yeah, even though it was like cold, it wasn't crunchy or fresh, it was still so tasty.
It was so tasty.
The food here is so good. It's so good.
I don't know what kind of miracle it is that I actually can eat it.
I don't know. It seems like it's okay. Maybe it's because I've been walking so much. I don't know.
It's it's crazy.
It's crazy.
Yeah, good news, right?
I don't know, maybe it is making me sick, but I'm like powering through it or something.
I still get really sleepy.
All right, I'm going to... um, I can't find any like cakes to put on there, but there's some really really good cake art. Thank you, thank you.
All right, let's continue with... um this, the fan book. And then I want to chat with you guys for a little bit,
just uh do some questions.
just do some questions.
And then that'll probably be it for birthday stream.
And then that'll probably be it for the birthday stream.
But yeah, I still want to chat. Ah, very cute. Happy birthday number one detective, by Jase. Thank you.
I went to eat ramen at a place and it was like a really small place and I was like one of the only people in there.
And uh I think it was the owner. The owner was there and he was like standing there with his arms crossed watching me.
And I was like really full already, but I was trying to eat as much as I could.
But uh afterwards, Chiara told me she's like, "Yeah, you're supposed to, you know, slurp really loudly."
And I was like trying to be quiet because you know, I I just didn't want to be like rude.
And I was like trying to be quiet because you know, I just didn't want to be like rude.
I don't know, cuz you know, if they see like a girl, they're like, oh, why are they being why are they being so messy?
You know, that sort of thing, but afterwards,
Chiara told me that um yeah, they like want to hear you slurp really loud.
Chiara told me that uh yeah, they like want to hear you slurp really loud.
Yeah, yeah, I was trying to be polite, but he was like staring me down as I was eating.
But it was good. It was kind of weird. It had like some It was like ground beef or something.
I don't know what it was, but I ate it.
I'm sorry, I'm going for another bite of my fruit sando.
The food here is the best! If you guys haven't been to Japan, I hope you can go at some point because the food is so good.
I feel like if I never went to another country, I'd probably just be satisfied.
Just cuz this is the first time I've ever gone anywhere.
This is the first time I've ever traveled anywhere, you know, aside from being brought over from Iggy ZooLand,
which is, if you guys know, you know.
So it was my first time.
is scary 'cause I thought maybe they would ask like why I was in the airport.
It's scary 'cause I thought maybe they would ask like why I was in the airport.
I thought that customs would maybe like question
whether or not, like, why? Why do you have a laptop? Why do you have a microphone? What What do you really doing here in Japan, you know?
But thankfully, nobody asked any questions.
So that was nice.
It was really simple.
It was very easy.
And a laptop's allowed. No, no, no, it's fine, it's fine.
Yeah, it's scary going the first time.
I'll be here for a little while, for a little while, and then I'm going to go back, and then, who knows? I might come again, come back again soon.
Happy birthday, Ame! I'll be have a wonderful birthday celebration this year, too!
It was pretty cool.
Watching your streams always brightens up my day.
Aw. I was being secure to watch. Check out your streams and other people in your community 'cause how friendly you taught them to be. Yeah.
You guys are being nice, right? Be nice to each other, huh?
And to the other fan base, too, right?
Yeah, yeah. Have I met with Iramo? Um, I met with Iramo,
um, it was it was also a few months ago I met with Iramo, uh, during our first myth off collab, but I haven't seen her yet.
This trip, not yet.
Not yet. Hopefully, though.
The amount of hard work you put in for your friends never fails to amaze me. Sometimes I even keep look out for random Bubba
appearing in 3D streams.
And they're working hard for them has been a long 2-year journey.
Well, and I'll never regret having been on.
Ah, thank you, thank you, thank you for the support all the way through, all the way through the journey.
Ya go meet up when?
Um, I might be able to meet Ya go at some point soon, I think, probably.
All right, let's see. And I want to meet Iris, too. I want to meet Iris.
I know the the BGM gets fuzzy.
And we'll see, maybe we'll meet some other senpais.
Hopefully, lots of people to meet, right?
Um, I remember following is brilliant and fantastic in their own ways, we sit out to me. Your fearlessness to be innovative,
and now, I can't even count how many times your streams have watched you charge something new or different, let's and all wondering how you even concocted this idea.
I'd be remiss if I didn't also mention your nefarious work behind the scenes, from orchestrating collaborations to doing camera work, VR streams,
when you guys are just sweet.
Thank you, anonymous teammate. Thank you.
Oh, cute. Oh, this cake. Oh, my god, I've I've had so much so much different types of cakes since I got here. So many different types of cakes.
I had an orange cake, I had Tiramisu, I had um a strawberry no, I don't think I've had a strawberry cake yet, but I had uh pistachio cheesecake.
Um, yeah, and I've tried like pretty much all the kombini food, and that's that was like the only thing I ate for the first two days.
I got here. I just had kombini food.
They have like cream puffs, they have uh really tasty onigiri, and these different sandwiches. Oh, like I have egg sando right now in my bag.
They're so good.
Right, you have to eat the kombini food because the 7-Eleven in the US, they just sell the stinky hot dogs, but here they have like a crispy chicken, a piece of crispy chicken, it's so tasty.
And they also have um what was it? Oh, yeah, I had curry the curry pan, curry bread.
So good. All the food here is so good.
And it a lot of it is like pretty cheap, too. And it's kind of crazy.
How much good food there is, we're not even that much.
Happy birthday, Millie, I have another fun year watching your stream. Aw.
Yes. Yes, now that New Year's started after I'm done travelling, uh there might be some more traveling, but then we'll get back to normal streams.
I want to play some games. At least we'll be playing Mario Kart later, although you guys will have to pretend you're watching me, okay?
Happy Birthday, Ame! May your special day be as epic and as sweet as you are!
Oh, this is so cute!
I like this bosun.
I like this bosun here.
Oh wait, can you guys see my cursor? I don't think so. Wait, can you?
You missed Japanese food? I could see why.
Oh my god, everything is so tasty!
I every time I go to bed, I'm just like so full.
Every time I go to bed, I'm just like so full.
It's a good thing I've been walking a lot, so I'm I'm like burning it off.
It's a good thing I've been walking a lot, so I'm like burning it off.
I decided that even if it was going to make me sick, I would still eat bread and stuff anyways.
Which seems like it's okay.
I mean I get really sleepy pretty early and then I just take a nap on the train and then I just keep going.
All right, let me take this last bite.
Maybe it's jet lag?
Mhm. Yeah, maybe.
And honestly, well, I got kind of lucky with my timing 'cause I have a friend group that's also visiting Japan.
And then, Hololive people as well.
So I just kind of tag along, but then it'll also just like go by myself.
And I'll get lost in some random street, but just keep walking 'cause everything is so... it's so interesting to look at, you know?
Even if it's... it's not like the usual tourist stuff,
I'm just going to like some of the backstreets and like the alleys and stuff like that.
And it's so nice.
It's fun to get lost.
Yeah, the best way to visit, right? No, not the backstreets.
Yeah, back alleys.
And, you know, like compared to the US, everything is so clean and the buildings are so cute.
I see some like vending machines that they look like I could pick them up, you know what I mean?
Oh my god! And I've done so much gacha, gacha, gachapon.
It... Eat that!
I've done so much gacha.
It's great.
Gacha everywhere!
Every time I see like a few, I'm just like, "Okay, hold on, let me pull out my coin purse."
Got anything good? Mhm. I did get some good stuff,
but I don't remember right now at the top of my head, so maybe it wasn't that good.
Is it cold in Japan? It's a little cold, but it's nice.
The wind is really cold. The wind is really cold.
Ooh.
Long hair Ame.
Art by Gin.
Thank you!
Yeah, cold is better than hot, right? Because it's like when you're hot, it can only take off so much clothes.
You can't take off your skin.
But when you're cold, you just put on more clothes, so easy.
Hi Ame, I'm a long time viewer of yours and lurker, meaning that I never seen my name in chat,
but I do love your content and streams. I watch streams you do since debut even though I can't spout.
I get membership, I still try to support your content by watching. Oops, and maybe
I'll be able to get a membership. Let's keep doing what you're doing, the streams are great and entertaining.
I'll just try to catch your streams. And, well, thank you.
Ariz... Aris T? I hope I said it right.
See, isn't that why gifted memberships are nice? Because look, some people can't get it, but they might get lucky in the chat and get some gifted ones. It's so sweet! Thank you so much.
Hey Ame, happy birthday! Your streams have gotten me through many hard days throughout the past two years,
and brightened many more. Inspiration to me in watching you motivate me to grow my creativity and work ethic, and my work ethic needs some work too.
Thank you for all your hard work and you putting into your projects and streams, looking forward to seeing what you do and accomplish in the future!
Ah, thank you! Rinskit.
Thank you for always working hard. Your smile gives happiness to many people. Thank you so much, Zaniia.
Actually, I have an asset that uh Zaniia made for me.
Is this like um... Hold on.
Ah, okay. I'll just leave it. Wait.
What did I do?
Wait, what did I do? Ah. Thank you for the gifts.
No, I wasn't trying to get you guys to get... Oh, I see.
'Cause it's supposed to be a book. Ah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is the other side.
Ah, thank you, thank you, thank you for the gifts.
Dear Ame, happy birthday Ame! Three birthdays already! Time flies by so fast. Oh, this is cute.
Oh, just like a scan of a letter.
Ah!
Uh, I hope the birthday girl's having a wonderful birthday.
Uh, I hope the birthday girl's
having a wonderful birthday.
Thank you for introducing the rest of Hololive to me, always so supportive of your friends and coworkers on branch, just as a whole Hololive.
Thank you for introducing the rest of Hololive to me,
always so supportive of your friends and coworkers...
And making us team mates feel like part of the big Hololive family.
...and making us teammates feel like
part of the big Hololive family.
Yeah!
When you debuted, I was still just a kid living in the toughest years of my life, seeing things I'd rather forget.
When you debuted, I was still just a kid
living in the toughest years of my life...
You coming to my live always streaming early morning in my time zone.
...seeing things I'd rather forget.
You coming to my live always streaming early morning...
Gave me something to look forward to every time I wake up, watching you streams start my day always brightens me up.
...gave me something to look forward to.
Every time I wake up, watching your streams...
Like you can be an adult,
...start my day, always brightens me up.
just this year.
Like, you can be an adult, just this year.
A kid were watching!
Your attitude and values to do things your own way, doing things you know is right for you, even when people tell you otherwise.
Your attitude and values to do things your own way,
doing things you know is right for you...
It's truly inspiration.
...even when people tell you otherwise.
It's truly an inspiration.
Your attitude has helped me made some important decisions.
Your attitude has helped me
make some important decisions.
Well, I'm glad I can help.
Keep working hard!
Yeah, growing up isn't easy, right?
Well, I'm glad you enjoyed the streams.
Thank you so much for all your support.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Oh, there's so much of this book, and I want to go through all of it, but I don't think we'll have time.
Oh, there's so much of this book,
and I want to go through all of it...
Oh, so cute!
...but I don't think we'll have time.
Gizmo!
Look at this cute art.
You know, there's someone you know met on the other side of the world the camera say, "I love you. What?"
You know, there's someone you met on the other side
of the world who can't even say, "I love you. What?"
Oh, so sweet!
So cute!
So cute so cute.
Daburu daburu daburu.
And the art is really good too.
Ah, so cute!
All right, all right, we'll be scrolling all day if we stay here, so I'm going to look at the rest off stream and um
All right, all right, we'll be scrolling all day
if we stay here, so I'm gonna look at the rest off-stream...
I think my manager mentioned something about possibly getting a actual printed version maybe at some point.
...and um, I think my manager mentioned something
about possibly getting an actual printed version...
So I'm looking forward to that actually holding it in my hands and I'm going to keep it on my coffee table. Is that weird?
...maybe at some point. So I'm looking forward to that,
actually holding it in my hands. I'm going to keep it on my coffee table. Is that weird?
I'm going to keep it on my coffee table.
Oh, thank you, thank you, thank you.
All right, are you guys playing your iPad?
Give me a second.
Give me one more moment.
Uh, hold on, they want to...
Uh, let's do this.
You guys are so sweet, thank you so much for all the work put into the fan book, it's really nice.
You guys are so sweet, thank you so much
for all the work put into the fan book.
It's really nice.
I can't wait to get a hard copy version.
I'm going to bring the crane up here,
but give me a second.
We'll put it right here.
Okay, just give me a second while I prepare.
One more thing, I'm going to do my
final announcement.
Final announcement, I believe,
because then it's time to get ready for Mario Kart.
Pa pa pa pa pa pa ya, pa pa pa pa ya, pa pa pa pa ya, pa pa pa.
Pa pa pa pa pa pa ya, pa pa pa pa ya,
pa pa pa pa ya, pa pa pa.
Pa pa pa pa pa pa ya, pa pa pa pa ya, pa pa pa pa ya, pa pa pa.
Pa pa pa pa pa pa ya, pa pa pa pa ya,
pa pa pa pa ya, pa pa pa.
Pa pa pa pa pa pa ya, pa pa pa pa ya, pa pa pa pa ya, pa pa pa pa ya...
Pa pa pa pa pa pa ya, pa pa pa pa ya,
pa pa pa pa ya, pa pa pa pa ya...
Pa pa pa pa pa pa ya, pa pa pa pa ya, pa pa pa pa ya, pa pa pa.
Pa pa pa pa pa pa ya, pa pa pa pa ya,
pa pa pa pa ya, pa pa pa.
Ah, looking for the perfect file.
Excuse me.
All right, we're going to hide uh
We're going to hide this for a second actually. Oh, let's see you guys get the last item.
We're going to hide this for a second actually.
Oh, let's have you guys get the last item.
Uh, Bubba! Bubba plushie.
All right, we'll pause.
Actually, let me move over, put it here for a second, it'll go this way.
Actually, let me move over, put it here for a second.
It'll go this way.
Oh, we'll put this here.
Okay, alright.
Okay, all right.
All right, you guys ready? We're going to play a game.
Now everything's ready.
Tada!
Wait. Tada!
Wait, you can't see it.
Tada!
Wait, can you guys see that?
Okay, there.
There we go. What is that? There's a new item on the screen.
There is a new item. Can you guys get that?
Are you guys able to grab that? I don't know. It's kind of in a weird spot, huh?
I need you guys to grab it.
Uh a little bit more to the right. Okay.
A little more to the right. You guys got the uh the concert start symbol really fast.
Really, really fast.
A little bit more to the right. Come on, come on.
Oh, you guys are so close. You're so close.
Right there, it's right there, it's right there!
Don't grab yet, don't grab yet.
The shadow, do you guys see the shadow? It's like almost on it.
You might be able to get it.
Oh, oh, right there, right there! Okay, grab!
Grab, grab, grab!
Uh okay, that should be good if you go that far.
Are you guys you guys are over it, I think.
Grab!
Oh, yatta! What is it?
Original song preview! I misspelled it.
That's right, I have an original song uh now, but it won't be releasing until...
...the 14th of January. So you guys do have to wait.
But I have some more uh surprises in store for that.
Hold on, I have a logo that I'm going to put here...
...which I totally did not prepare beforehand. But I do have a little preview...
...that I'm going to show you guys.
Just give me a second while I put this on the screen.
An original song, finally!
And here it is.
It's called... wait, let me move...
...the let me move this over.
It's called...
Tada! Chiku Taku, which means tick-tock.
But it's not, you know, it's uh chiku chiku taku. It's not tick-tock. Chiku taku.
Okay, I'm going to play a little preview for you guys. There's no vocals, but...
...um it's a really nice preview and you guys will have to wait until...
January 14th PST.
It'll be um January 15th JST.
Uh you guys will have to wait to hear it then.
But for now, please listen. Hopefully it doesn't get fuzzy, but please listen.
Okay, I'm going to play it one more time 'cause last time it got messed up. Okay, from the beginning, one more time.
Yay!
So yeah, that's a it's it's kind of a different mix um
So yeah, that's a... it's kind of a different mix, um
But, you guys will be able to hear the full original song, obviously with vocals,
but you guys will be able to hear the full original song,
uh on January 14th.
obviously with vocals, on January 14th.
So, please listen and please wait for the music video premiere
on January 14th. I just had to delay it a little bit uh to finish up something for it.
on January 14th. I just had to delay it a little bit to finish up something for it.
But you guys will see. And yeah, I have some more surprises in store
But you guys will see. And yeah,
uh on that day. So we'll do another stream for sure on that day
I have some more surprises in store on that day,
um during the premiere and we'll do like a watchalong and yeah, some other stuff.
so we'll do another stream for sure on that day during the premiere and do a watchalong and, yeah, some other stuff.
So yeah, it kind of goes like...
All right, I can't wait for you guys to hear it, the official version, so yes, please look forward to it.
All right, I can't wait for you guys to hear the official version, so yes, please look forward to it.
And I'm going to end the stream right about now, uh as the pin message showed before,
And I'm going to end the stream right about now, as the pin message showed before,
the merch cup pin uh I will be reading super chats at a later day. I'd like to read them
the merch cup pin... I will be reading super chats at a later date. I'd like to read them
even though I'm going to have a lot, a lot piled up, but uh I'd still like to do it anyways.
even though I'm going to have a lot, a lot piled up, but I'd still like to do it anyways.
Um, so thank you guys so much for all your support
and thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you. Arigato gozaimasu.
Thank you.
And we still have some more exciting stuff later in the month. So, yeah, clubs
And we still have some more exciting stuff later in the month. So, yeah, collabs,
off clubs for whatever original song.
off-collabs for whatever original song.
Yatta! And thank you so much to all the people that made this possible.
Um thank you Hima for your help and thank you kind of for the concert
Um, thank you Hima for your help, and thank you Kawa for the concert,
and C-Foam for uh help with the 3D stuff.
and C-Foam for help with the 3D stuff.
And this is Wondoriku who did the um the song that you guys will be able to hear.
And this is Wondoriku who did the song that you guys will be able to hear.
And I feel like I'm forgetting a lot of people. No rough pro does, yeah.
And I feel like I'm forgetting a lot of people. No, Rough Diamond does, yeah.
Thank you and to everybody that helped and to all of you guys with the fan book.
Thank you to everybody that helped, and to all of you guys with the fan book.
Thank you so much. Hello Cali, a thank you.
Thank you so much. Hello Callie, thank you.
And A-chan's gift card, oh thank you.
おき おじだ OK
Okay, time to... Okay!
All right, goodbye everyone. Thank you again for watching.
If you are interested in the merch, it's now available for sale on the link pinned in the chat.
If you're interested in the merch, it's now available for sale at the link pinned in the chat.
And I'll see you guys very soon. Okay, thank you again for all your support. Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you!
And I'll see you guys very soon. Okay, thank you again for all your support. Thank you, thank you, thank you!
GOT SMOL AME!!!
GOT WATSON CONCOCTION!!!
GOT BUBBA PLUSHY!!!
GOT BYE BYE!!!!